<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<source>
   <job>
      <title>SEMH Support Assistant - Portsmouth</title>
      <referencenumber>ETC2101-322</referencenumber>
      <description>As an SEMH Learning Support Assistant, you will play a vital role in helping students overcome barriers to learning. You will be responsible for supporting pupils with SEMH needs on a 1:1 or small group basis, helping them stay focused and engaged while managing behavior positively within the classroom.</description>
      <location>Portsmouth, Hampshire</location>
      <company>EduTalent Connect</company>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>SEMH Support Assistant - Maidenhead</title>
      <referencenumber>ETC2101-323</referencenumber>
      <description>Empower young people as an SEMH Learning Support Assistant. You will assist teachers in delivering tailored support to ensure all pupils feel included and motivated. You will help students navigate social challenges and stay focused on their learning objectives.</description>
      <location>Maidenhead, Berkshire</location>
      <company>EduTalent Connect</company>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>SEMH Support Assistant - Crowthorne</title>
      <referencenumber>ETC2101-324</referencenumber>
      <description>Make an impact in secondary education as an SEMH LSA. You will support lesson engagement for students requiring additional emotional support and help manage behavior in line with school policies. This role requires patience, resilience, and a passion for supporting youth.</description>
      <location>Crowthorne, Berkshire</location>
      <company>EduTalent Connect</company>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>SEMH Support Assistant - Windsor</title>
      <referencenumber>ETC2101-325</referencenumber>
      <description>Make an impact in secondary education as an SEMH LSA. You will support lesson engagement for students requiring additional emotional support and help manage behavior in line with school policies. This role requires patience, resilience, and a passion for supporting youth.</description>
      <location>Windsor, Berkshire</location>
      <company>EduTalent Connect</company>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>SEMH Support Assistant - Eton</title>
      <referencenumber>ETC2101-326</referencenumber>
      <description>Seeking an empathetic SEMH Support Assistant to work with secondary pupils. You will reinforce lesson content, help maintain positive classroom routines, and provide a stable presence for students facing emotional or social difficulties.</description>
      <location>Eton, Berkshire</location>
      <company>EduTalent Connect</company>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Sports Coach LSA - Bridport</title>
      <referencenumber>ETC2101-327</referencenumber>
      <description>Use your coaching background to support secondary students as a Sports Coach LSA. You will help break down learning tasks and encourage teamwork and focus in the classroom. This is a great opportunity to be a positive role model while supporting academic progress.</description>
      <location>Bridport, Dorset</location>
      <company>EduTalent Connect</company>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Sports Coach LSA - Portslade-by-Sea</title>
      <referencenumber>ETC2101-328</referencenumber>
      <description>Join our team as a Sports Coach LSA and help students progress to the best of their ability. You will support positive classroom routines and help manage behavior using techniques gained from your sports and coaching experience.</description>
      <location>Portslade-by-Sea, East Sussex</location>
      <company>EduTalent Connect</company>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Sports Coach LSA - Ferndown</title>
      <referencenumber>ETC2101-329</referencenumber>
      <description>Support students' focus and organization in a secondary setting. Ideal for those with a background in sports coaching or youth work, this role involves assisting teachers and providing guidance to students who benefit from an active and structured approach.</description>
      <location>Ferndown, Dorset</location>
      <company>EduTalent Connect</company>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Sports Coach LSA - Slough</title>
      <referencenumber>ETC2101-330</referencenumber>
      <description>Combine education and athletics in this Sports Coach LSA role. You will support students with their learning while promoting physical health and teamwork, helping to create an inclusive and dynamic classroom environment.</description>
      <location>Slough, Berkshire</location>
      <company>EduTalent Connect</company>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Sports Coach LSA - Crowthorne</title>
      <referencenumber>ETC2101-331</referencenumber>
      <description>Work alongside teaching staff as a Sports Coach LSA to support positive behavior and classroom participation. You will help students stay engaged with classroom activities and reinforce lesson objectives using a proactive and energetic approach.</description>
      <location>Crowthorne, Berkshire</location>
      <company>EduTalent Connect</company>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Teaching Assistant - Bexhill-on-Sea</title>
      <referencenumber>ETC2101-332</referencenumber>
      <description>Join a supportive secondary school as a Teaching Assistant. You will assist with lesson preparation and provide direct support to pupils, helping them overcome academic challenges and stay focused on their learning journey.</description>
      <location>Bexhill-on-Sea, East Sussex</location>
      <company>EduTalent Connect</company>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Teaching Assistant - Hailsham</title>
      <referencenumber>ETC2101-333</referencenumber>
      <description>Work in a welcoming school team as a Teaching Assistant. You will support pupils academically and pastorally, assisting with classroom organization and helping to maintain a positive and productive learning environment for all students.</description>
      <location>Hailsham, East Sussex</location>
      <company>EduTalent Connect</company>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Teaching Assistant - Wareham</title>
      <referencenumber>ETC2101-334</referencenumber>
      <description>Work in a welcoming school team as a Teaching Assistant. You will support pupils academically and pastorally, assisting with classroom organization and helping to maintain a positive and productive learning environment for all students.</description>
      <location>Wareham, Dorset</location>
      <company>EduTalent Connect</company>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Teaching Assistant - Crowborough</title>
      <referencenumber>ETC2101-335</referencenumber>
      <description>Provide targeted support to secondary students as a Teaching Assistant. You will help clarify instructions, reinforce lesson content, and assist students with written and practical tasks to ensure they remain engaged and progressing.</description>
      <location>Crowborough, East Sussex</location>
      <company>EduTalent Connect</company>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Teaching Assistant - Weymouth</title>
      <referencenumber>ETC2101-336</referencenumber>
      <description>Engage with students to help them access learning. This Teaching Assistant role involves providing essential support during lessons, ensuring that every pupil feels motivated and capable of completing their schoolwork effectively.</description>
      <location>Weymouth, Dorset</location>
      <company>EduTalent Connect</company>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Cover Supervisor - Wokingham</title>
      <referencenumber>ETC2101-337</referencenumber>
      <description>Seeking confident individuals to work as Cover Supervisors. You will follow school behavior and safeguarding policies while supervising classroom activities, ensuring that pupils stay focused and respectful throughout the lesson.</description>
      <location>Wokingham, Berkshire</location>
      <company>EduTalent Connect</company>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Cover Supervisor - Petersfield</title>
      <referencenumber>ETC2101-338</referencenumber>
      <description>Join our team as a Cover Supervisor and deliver pre-set work to secondary students. You will ensure learning continues smoothly during teacher absences, managing classroom routines and building a positive rapport with students.</description>
      <location>Petersfield, Hampshire</location>
      <company>EduTalent Connect</company>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Cover Supervisor - Rye</title>
      <referencenumber>ETC2101-339</referencenumber>
      <description>Gain valuable classroom experience as a Cover Supervisor. You will manage classroom behavior and ensure that pre-set work is completed, providing a consistent and stable learning space for students aged 11-16 across various subjects.</description>
      <location>Rye, East Sussex</location>
      <company>EduTalent Connect</company>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Cover Supervisor - Swanage</title>
      <referencenumber>ETC2101-340</referencenumber>
      <description>Rewarding role for those looking to work in education. As a Cover Supervisor, you will manage behavior and promote student responsibility, helping to create an environment where learning can continue effectively without interruption.</description>
      <location>Swanage, Dorset</location>
      <company>EduTalent Connect</company>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Cover Supervisor - Portsmouth</title>
      <referencenumber>ETC2101-341</referencenumber>
      <description>Support local secondary schools as a Cover Supervisor. This role involves supervising classes, maintaining order, and ensuring that all students are engaged with their assigned work in a safe and respectful manner.</description>
      <location>Portsmouth, Hampshire</location>
      <company>EduTalent Connect</company>
   </job>
</source>
